<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AustinTourGuide</string>
    <string name="title_historic">Historic</string>
    <string name="title_food">Food</string>
    <string name="title_attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="title_festivals">Festivals</string>
    <string name="historic_bartonSprings_description">Early Austin businessman and philanthropist Andrew Jackson Zilker gifted the citizens of Austin with Zilker Park, a 360-acre oasis in the heart of downtown that’s the site of festivals and free music at Zilker Hillside Theater, plus it’s home to Zilker Botanical Garden, Umlauf Sculpture Garden and Museum and Barton Springs Pool, a spring-fed swimming spot with grassy hills for sunbathing.</string>
    <string name="historic_bartonSprings_address">Address: 2131 William Barton Dr, Austin, TX 78746</string>
    <string name="historic_bartonSprings_name">Barton Springs Pool</string>
    <string name="historic_paramount_name">Paramount Theatre</string>
    <string name="historic_paramount_description">The Paramount Theatre is a century-old performance venue and movie theater located in the heart of downtown Austin.</string>
    <string name="historic_paramount_address">Address: 713 Congress Ave, Austin, TX 78701</string>
    <string name="historic_bridge_name">Congress Avenue Bridge</string>
    <string name="historic_bridge_description">Originally built in 1910, today the Ann W. Richards Congress Avenue Bridge is known as the home of a colony of 1.5 million Mexican free-tailed bats that spectacularly fly out into the night sky every evening from spring through fall.</string>
    <string name="historic_bridge_address">Address: Congress Ave, Austin, TX 78704</string>
    <string name="food_hollaMode_name">Holla Mode</string>
    <string name="food_hollaMode_description">This friendly food trailer brings the flavors of Thailand to Austin. Thai-style ice cream is made to order by pouring your choice of dairy or coconut milk onto a steel plate chilled to -30°F. Once frozen into a thin layer, the ice cream is scraped into rolls and garnished with your choice of “chops” that include fruit, cookies and candies, along with toppings such as whipped cream and rainbow sprinkles.</string>
    <string name="food_hollaMode_address">Address: 1800 Barton Springs Rd, Austin, TX 78704</string>
    <string name="food_hayElotes_name">Hay Elotes</string>
    <string name="food_hayElotes_description">There are lots of Mexican treats to choose from here, but don’t pass up the Fresas Con Crema, a deliciously sweet confection of strawberries and cream. The cream is a mix of condensed milk, Mexican sour cream and sugar that’s dotted with diced strawberries. Top it off whipped cream, chopped nuts and even more fruit, such as blueberries or raspberries.</string>
    <string name="food_hayElotes_address">Address: 2214 E 7th St, Austin, TX 78702</string>
    <string name="food_steelCity_name">Steel City Pops</string>
    <string name="food_steelCity_description">Steel City Pops is known for its variety of fruity frozen treats. The pops are made with fresh fruit and organic cane sugar, and include unique flavors like Champagne White Tea and Mango Habanero. Creamy pops like the citrusy Avocado and cookie pops such as Strawberry Shortcake are also offered. Customize your pop with a dip in dark chocolate or dust it with sea salt.</string>
    <string name="food_steelCity_address">Address:3001 Guadalupe St. Austin, TX 78705</string>
    <string name="attractions_zoo_name">Austin Zoo</string>
    <string name="attractions_zoo_description">The mission of Austin Zoo is to assist animals in need through rescue, rehabilitation and education. Located on the southwest edge of Austin off of Highway 290 West and Circle Drive, Austin Zoo is a pleasant Hill Country zoo where visitors from around the world can come to learn about animals close-up, spend some time outdoors getting exercise and have fun.</string>
    <string name="attractions_zoo_address">Address: 10808 Rawhide Tr. Austin, TX 78736</string>
    <string name="attractions_kayaks_name">Congress Avenue Kayaks</string>
    <string name="attractions_kayaks_description">Congress Avenue Kayaks is a locally-owned business boasting more than five years of providing Austinites and visitors alike with fun, positive outdoor recreational experiences via kayaks and standup paddleboards on downtown Austin’s Lady Bird Lake (Town Lake). Located at the Waller Creek Boathouse on the Ann and Roy Butler Hike and Bike Trail next to Lady Bird Lake, Congress Avenue Kayaks is open daily year round with hourly rentals, guided tours, classes, and private lessons.</string>
    <string name="attractions_kayaks_address">Address: 74 Trinity St. Austin, TX 78701</string>
    <string name="attractions_zip_name">Zip Lost Pines</string>
    <string name="attractions_zip_description">Inspiring and filled with adventure for you and yours, soar side-by-side over shady pine forests and across steep canyons while catching a glimpse of the mighty “Texas” Colorado river and local wildlife. This Austin-area zip line experience features 6 dual zip lines, 3 suspension bridges and access to McKinney Roughs Nature Park. Zip Lost Pines features the longest side-by-side zip line tour experience in Texas, with the longest line measuring ¼ of a mile!</string>
    <string name="attractions_zip_address">Address: 1760 Hwy. 71 W. Cedar Creek, TX 78612</string>
    <string name="festivals_bat_name">Bat Fest (8/18/18)</string>
    <string name="festivals_bat_description">Celebrate this batty event as the worlds largest urban bat colony (two million Mexican Free Tail bats which take up seasonal residence beneath the Congress Avenue Bridge) take to the skies for their nightly flight. Enjoy live music, children\\'s activities and a costume contest.</string>
    <string name="festivals_bat_address">Where: Congress Avenue Bridge</string>
    <string name="festivals_parade_name">Austin Pride Parade and Festival (9/25/18)</string>
    <string name="festivals_parade_description">The PRIDE Festival is the largest annual LGBTQ advocacy and fundraising event in Central Texas! Dozens of non-profit organizations and social clubs use the Festival as a platform to inform and interact with the thousands of attendees. Each year, countless people find new organizations to join, causes to support and opportunities to volunteer.</string>
    <string name="festivals_parade_address">Where: Fiesta Gardens and Downtown Austin</string>
    <string name="festivals_acl_name">Austin City Limits Music Festival (10/5 – 10/7 and 10/12 - 10/14)</string>
    <string name="festivals_acl_description">One of the countrys largest celebrations of live music, this two weekend, six day festival brings the magic of the famed public TV series "Austin City Limits" outside the studio and into Austin's most beloved park. More than 150 musical acts will take over eight stages along with local food vendors, brewers, artists and pop up shops and artists.</string>
    <string name="festivals_acl_address">Where: Zilker Park</string>
</resources>
